sgtsearch.com 2005-04-08

# SgtSearch.com - Privacy Policy and Terms of Website Usage.

|  **SgtSearch Legal Information - Please read carefully**  
  
---  
Terms of Use \- Outlines the terms of use for ALL users.  
Privacy Policy \- We really DO care about your privacy.  

* * *

SgtSearch has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy. The only reason we collect information from our end users is to add their resource to our directory, or allow them to recieve our infrequent newsletters. We refuse to entertain the idea, nor do we intend to sell any information we receive. Please don't bother asking. 

**Use of Internet Protocol Address**

* * *

We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, to help identify you and your submissions, and to gather broad demographic information. You should know that an I.P. address can not be used to identify who you are. The I.P. address tells us relative information such as : (i)which country you access our site from, (ii) who your internet provider may be, and (iii) how often you visit us. We do not wish to identify you, and only use this address to enhance our offerings. 

**Use of Registration Information**

* * *

Our site's registration area (site submission) requires visitors to supply contact information, such as name ,e-mail address , website and zip codes. We use this information to list your website in our directory and may send you promotional email from our company and from some of our partners, contained in our mailings. However, users may opt in , or out of these promotional e-mail messages at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) We do not add you to any list without your consent. You will only receive emails regarding your submission unless you opt to receive more email from us. 

**Use of Demographic Information**

* * *

We may, from time to time also collect demographic and profile data that we use to tailor your experience at SgtSearch. Based on this information, we display products and content we feel you might interest you. This information will always be supplied on a volunteer basis. Information you submit when you add a resource (website listing) is also used to better enhance our website. Should you supply feedback, this would be an example of us using information submitted by you to make your visit more enjoyable. We will not attempt to indetify you regardless of any information you send us, unless you explicity wish to be indentified. (example - you wish to create a business partnership) 

**Use of Submission Information**

* * *

When you submit websites, SgtSearch requests information such as contact information, website and possibly demographic information. The contact information you provide is used to send you updates, company information and promotional material from us or our partners from time to time. You can opt out or opt in at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.)   
Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services. (applies to paid advertisers only) Demographic data is collected to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would interest you most. 

**Use of Online Survey Information**

* * *

To participate in our online surveys, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. SgtSearch uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would most interest you. 

**Use of Information Collected in Contests**

* * *

To participate in our contests, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. SgtSearch uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Again - demographic and profile data are collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel you would most interest you. 

**Public Forums Guidelines**

* * *

SgtSearch may offer chat rooms and bulletin boards. Please note that information that is disclosed in these arenas becomes public. Use caution in disclosing any personal information. 

**Security**

* * *

When you submit sites, a zip code and first name is required, however no address is collected. This data and other information such as email addresses are protected by several access levels of encryption. 

**Children's Guidelines**

* * *

We **do not** collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We **do not** distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We **do not** give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We **do not** entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information. 

**Opt Out/Opt In**

* * *

SgtSearch allows users to opt out of receiving e-mail from us or our partners. To opt out of our mailing list you can simply click on the link at the bottom of your emails. This link will be sent with every newsletter mailing. 

**Correct/Update Personal Information**

* * *

SgtSearch allows you to change or modify your personal information by contacting us via our contact page. You can also use this contact area to change your listing, should the change meet our criteria. At any time we may offer or deny the ability to access any information in our database. We will however, completely remove any individual record at that individuals request. 

**Disclaimer**

* * *

This site contains links to other sites. SgtSearch is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

**Contact Us**

* * *

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us:   
ATTEN : Privacy Concern to Webmaster at SgtSearch.com 

**This policy was last updated January 25th, 2005.**  
  
---
